xfxforce.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy

XFX is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We’ve structured our Web site so that you can visit us without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. 

Should you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with XFX. For instance, when you provide personal information through the myXFX service, we use the information for internal use only. We do not provide it to anyone outside XFX. 

### Awareness

XFX provides this Online Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy policy, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

### What We Collect

You can order products and services, make requests, and register to receive materials from the XFXforce.com Web site. The types of personal information collected from these pages are: name, email, business contact, address and demographic information, such as age, gender, occupation and education level. Information pertaining to the type of XFX product and other computer equipment may also be collected. 

Please note that the information submitted to XFX via the Web may be processed and/or stored outside of the country in which it was submitted. 

Some XFXforce.com web pages use cookies, a data analysis technique. Learn more about how we use cookies. 

### How We Use Your Information

XFX uses your information to better understand your needs and to provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, for product registration purposes, for promotions or contests, or to personalize our Web sites for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. The information is not disclosed to anyone outside of XFX and is stored in a secure environment. 

From time to time we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with the information we think would be of particular interest. We will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct information. 

### Who We Share It With

XFX will NOT sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other XFX entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described in “how we use it.” Such XFX entities and/or business partners, including those in Canada and the United States and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements. 

Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide when you register your ownership of XFX products. 

### Third Party Operators

Please note that certain areas of Web site may be operated by third parties. Whenever this is the case, please refer to the privacy statement of the third party to understand how your personally identifiable information is treated by that party. 

### Choice

XFX will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct information from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests. 

Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy. 

### Accuracy and Access

XFX strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable efforts to provide you with online access to our registration data so that you may view, update or correct your information at the XFX site where it was submitted. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. To access your personally identifiable information, return to the Web page where you originally entered it and follow the instructions on that Web page. 

### Links to Third Party Web Sites

Links to third party Web sites on the XFXForce.com site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the XFX site. XFX has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control, nor is it responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. Thus, XFX does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained by using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the XFXForce.com site, you do so at your own risk. 

### Security

XFX is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### Oversight

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us via email and use the word Privacy in the subject line. 

### How XFX Uses Cookies

A cookie is a piece of text asking permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. If you agree, then your browser adds the text in a small file. We may use cookies to enhance the user experience and deliver personalized content. Cookies help us to deliver information specific to your interests, to eliminate the need to re-enter your password each time you visit our site, or to keep track of your shopping cart. Cookies also allow us to better analyze our Web site traffic patterns so that we can improve our Web offerings. We do not follow your browsing path outside of the XFXforce.com Web site. Please note that certain areas of our Web site may be operated by third parties, in which case you should refer to that party’s Web site for information on how they use cookies. 

You may set your Web browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests or to decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contain cookies; those files are stored as part of your Internet browser.
